I am a senior studying computer science and business administration. I have academic experience in a range of technology fundamentals and programming languages. I have worked hard to build a track record of academic achievement and engagement at the high school and collegiate level. I have also participated in multiple Hackathons and I have completed multiple programming projects in my free time. In addition to my academic accomplishments, I have experience in a range of jobs which have helped me develop leadership and teamwork skills as well as the ability to adapt to diverse work environments.

EXPERIENCE

Vee24 — Engineering Intern - Boston, MA

Summer 2020, 2021

- Member of the Engineering team, working to write and improve software for cloud virtual
- Helped develop java mobile app using Android Studio. App designed to showcase the Vee24 software platform. Managed software revision control using Git/Github.
- Debugged and improved scripts using Python to identify problem patterns in production logs.

Gentle Giant Moving Co – Mover/Driver - Somerville, MA

2019-2021

- Member of moving teams responsible for execution of residential and commercial moving services.
 Trained, tested and gained Class D license and expanded responsibilities to include driving trucks to and from residences.
- Worked directly with customers during service delivery to assure highest satisfaction level. Followed customer instructions about placement of items and special considerations for handling.

Joe Pizza - Chef/Trainer - Medford, MA

2014-2018

- Chef and 5-year member of staff within a small, high volume family business. Worked successfully in close quarters under high pressure environment, often with newly hired staff-in-training.
- Established highly valued expertise managing pizza ovens while overseeing team members in other food preparation functions. Trained new team members. Longest tenured employee at time of my departure.

Fidelity House - Camp Counselor - Arlington, MA

Summer 2017

- Lead Counselor during all-day summer camp program responsible for supervision and safety of school aged children from 5 to 12 years of age.
- Daily challenges varied widely depending on the assigned group, age range, weather and planned activities which incorporated multi location, indoor/outdoor and remote field trips.

EDUCATION

Fordham U. - B.S. Computer Science 2022, Gabelli Business Minor Bronx, NY

Relevant Coursework: CS 1 &2, Discrete Structures 1, Data Structures, Java Programming, Algorithms, Databases, Operating Systems

Key Subject Matter: C++, Java, NetBeans, React JS, SQL, Python, CSS, HTML, Eclipse, Visual Studio,

Extra Curricular: Computer Science Society, Intramural Basketball, Club Frisbee, Flag Football, Deans List

Malden Catholic H.S. 2014-2018

Malden, MA

Academics: National Honor Society, Spanish National Honor Society, 99th percentile in Spanish National Language Exam.

Extracurricular: Freshman and JV Basketball; Two Years Outdoor Track Team, Captain, MVP Spring 2018; President, Spanish Club. Teaching assistant, St Raphael's religious education program.